我父母去世前 和我讲过这世界曾经的模样
Before they died, my parents told me stories about the world once was.
讲的是远在我出生之前的故事
How it was, long before I was born.
是与机器交战之前的往事
Before the war with the machines.
他们记得一个绿色的世界
They remember a green world,
广阔而美丽
vast and beautiful,
充满欢笑
filled with laughter,
以及对未来的希望
and hope for the future.
那是一个我永不得见的世界
It was a world I never know.
在我出生时
By the time I was born,
这一切
all this,
已荡然无存
was gone.
天网
Skynet,
一个被设计为自动防御导弹的电脑程序
a computer program designed to automate missile defense.
它本该保护我们
It was supposed to protect us.
但事与愿违
That's not what happened.
1997年8月29日 天网觉醒了
On August 29, 1997 Skynet woke up.
判定所有人类威胁着它的存在
And decided all humanity was a threat to its existence.
《终结者：创世纪》
它用我们的导弹攻击我们
It used our own bombs against us.
30亿人在核战火中丧生
Three billion people died in nuclear fire.
幸存的人们称那一天为审判日
The survivors called it Judgement Day.
人们如同老鼠般生活在暗影之中
People lived like rats in the shadows,
藏匿 挨饿 或是更糟
hiding, starving, or worse,
被抓进集中营灭杀
captured and put into camps for extermination.
我出生于审判日之后的世界
I was born after Judgement Day,
这是一个破碎的世界
into a broken world,
被机器所统治
ruled by the machines.
更可怕的是能伪装成人类的渗透单位
The worse were infiltration units, designed to pass for humans.
我们把它们叫作终结者
We called them Terminators.
没事了 伙计
Its okay, buddy.
乖孩子
Good boy.
这里有别人吗
Are the others down here?
于是一个男人发现了我
And then one man found me.
他叫约翰·康纳
His name is John Connor.
他改变了一切
And he changed everything.
（2029年 洛杉矶）
约翰教我们如何反击
John showed us how to fight back,
如何奋勇而起
how to rise up.
他解救了被囚禁的人们
He freed prisoners
他教我们如何摧毁机器
He taught us to smash the machines to scrap.
人们在私下谈论约翰
People whisper about John
好奇他的本事如何而来
wonder how he can know the things he does
人们形容他为先知
They use words like, prophet
但约翰不只如此
but John is more.
我们聚集于此 是因为今晚他将带领我们摧毁天网
We're here because tonight he's gonna lead us to crush Skynet.
永绝其害
For good.
长官 我请求加入科罗拉多进攻部队
Sir, request to join the Colorado Offensive.
我需要你在我身边 里斯
I need you with me, Reese.
彻底摧毁天网事关重大 长官
We're talking about the complete destruction of Skynet, Sir.
科罗拉多部队会成功的
The Colorado Unit will succeed.
机器会在今晚战败
The machines will fall tonight.
洛杉矶这边的攻击任务同样重要 或许更为重要
Right here, the Los Angeles assault is just as important is just as important too, maybe more.
比摧毁天网中央核心还重要？
More than destroying Skynet's central core?
约翰 我不明白你为什么要带人进攻一个劳动集中营
John, I don't understand why you're leading an attack on a workcamp?
因为这集中营是一个掩饰手段
Because the camp is a camoflauge.
集中营内有一个机库
Inside the camp is a hangar.
机库下面藏有天网的终极武器
Beneath the hangar, Skynet's hidden it's final weapon
一旦天网意识到败局已定 就会用这武器来确保它自己的存活
When Skynet realizes it is lost It"ll deploy that weapon to insure it's own survival
我们要今晚拿下它 否则时不再来
We take it tonight, there is no tomorrow.
我们会拿下的
Then we'll take it.
你是我的得力帮手 里斯 而我从没谢过你
You're my right hand, Reese, I never thank you for it.
你不用道谢
You don't need to.
你给了我们未来 约翰
You gave us all a future, John.
我要用上我的未来
I'm going to use mine.
这一切结束后
When this is all over, I'm…
我要去找我父母的房子
I'm going to find my parent's house.
重建它
Re-build it.
用我的双手做些杀戮之外的事
Use my hands, for something other than killing.
你呢
How about you?
喝冰啤酒好了
Cold beer will be good
- 这就是你的完美计划？- 没错
- That's your perfect plan? - Yes.
- 我想我没怎么想过这种事 - 看得出来
- Yeah, I guess I dont think about it too much. - Yeah, I can see that.
我想无论如何
I figure whatever happens,
都会比现在好
It's gonna be better than this.
为了走到这一步 我们牺牲了很多人
So many of us have died, to get here.
我希望你明白 凯尔 我要有别的办法 就早付诸行动了
I want you to know that, Kyle, if there was another way, I would have taken it.
出发
Move out.
机器认为
The machine thinks
我们无法获胜
that we can not win.
机器认为 我们不会
The machine thinks, that we will not
攻击
strike
天网核心
at the very heart of Skynet.
然而我们将在此
Yet here we stand
打响最终的生死之战
on the precipices of the final battle.
如果我们在今晚覆灭
If we die tonight,
那么人类将一同灭亡
mankind dies with us.
（功能失效）
动手
Now.
我在你们每一个人的身上
I look at each of you,
看到了这场漫长恶战带来的伤痕
And I see the marks of this long and terrible war.
前进 前进
Go, go.
警戒区已被突破
Perimeter breach.
激活101号机型
Activate model 101.
为我们的孩子而战
For our children.
为我们的后辈而战 这样他们就不会拥有这些伤痕
Our children's children. So they will not carry these marks.
但他们会知道我们的身份 我们的事迹
But they will know who we are, and what we did!
他们会知道我们不曾低头 我们不曾屈服
That we did not bow down. We did not give in.
我们曾在这一时 这一刻 奋勇而起
We rose up. At this moment. At this hour!
甘愿牺牲一切
Willing to sacrifice everything
因此他们才得以自由生活
So that they could live in freedom!
今晚 我们要夺回我们的世界
On this night, we take back our world!
它们在使用那个武器
They're using the weapon
我们得去机库
We got to get to the hangar.
约翰
John!
尝尝我的厉害吧
You want me? I'm right here.
科罗拉多部队报告 天网中央核心已被攻陷
Colorado unit reporting in. Skynet's central core is down.
重复 天网已被摧毁
Repeat: Skynet has been destroyed.
约翰说得没错
John was right.
科罗拉多部队成功了
Colorado units succeeded
机器战败了
and the machines fell.
但为时已晚
But it was too late.
我们找到它了 长官
We found it, Sir.
就在你说的那个地方
Right where you said it would be.
那是什么东西
What is that thing?
命运
The fate.
这是第一代战术时间武器
It is the first tactical time weapon.
天网刚使用了它
Skynet just used it.
（1984年 洛杉矶）
（凌晨 1点52分）
什么情况
What the hell?
我们需要十五分钟来准备好这台机器 长官
We'll need fifteen minutes to ready the machine, sir.
我们在计算坐标 马上就有结果了
We are running co-ordinates, we should have them for you momentarily.
1984年 洛杉矶
Los Angeles, 1984.
1984年 5月12日
Los Angeles, May 12…
洛杉矶
1984.
天网知道它将战败 所以它想耍手段操纵战局
Skynet knew it was losing. So tried to rig the game.
派了一个终结者回到战前
Sent a terminator back to the time before the war.
那目标是谁
Then who's the target?
我的母亲
My mother.
莎拉·康纳
Sarah Connor.
要是机器得逞 我就不会出生
If the machine suceeds, I'll never be born.
它们会先杀了她
They'll kill her first.
这样的话 我们每一场奋战而来的胜利都将不复存在
And by doing so, erase every victory we fought for,
包括今晚在内
including tonight's.
就不会有反抗军对抗机器
There won't be a Resistance to challenge the machines.
天网会因此获胜
With this one act Skynet will win.
我们能用这技术派人回去
We could use the technology ourselves, send someone back.
我们都不知道那是否能行
We don't even know if that'll work.
- 我去 - 我去 长官
- I'll go. - I'll go, sir.
- 派我去 长官 - 让我去
- I'll go, sir. - I'll go.
- 派我去 - 我去
- I'll go. - I'll go.
我自愿回去
I'll volunteer.
派我回去
I'll go back.
我为什么要派你去
Why should I send you?
而不是其他人
Over all of them?
因为我愿为莎拉·康纳而死
Cuz I'd die for Sarah Connor.
这里所有的人都愿为莎拉·康纳而死
All these people would die for Sarah Connor.
你又有什么不同
What makes you any different?
你知道原因
You know why.
你和我讲述过她的一切 我了解她 约翰
Everything you told me about her. I know her, John.
让我去救她
Let me save her.
不能带武器？
No weapons?
我们测量了磁场 它会撕裂所有未被活体组织包覆的物体
We've measured the magnetic field.It'll rip apart anything not in case in living tissue.
想像下把锡纸放进几十亿倍磁场强度的微波炉里
Think tinfoil in a microwave. Times a few billion.
只会留下坑洞
Nothing left but the crater.
也不能有衣物
No clothes, either.
她会当我疯了的
She's gonna think I'm crazy.
你知道这设备的地点
You knew the device would be here.
知道它设定的时间
You knew when it would be set for.
也知道机器会在今晚战败
You knew the machines would fall tonight.
在我走之前 告诉我吧
Before I go, tell me.
告诉你什么
Tell you what?
你看见未来了吗
Do you see the future?
没人能看见未来 里斯
No one can see the future, Reese.
好吧 那你是怎么知道的
Ok, then how do you know?
我有人指点
I cheat.
莎拉告诉过我很多事 她给了我指引
Sarah told me so much. She gave me signposts.
在我小的时候 我母亲就似乎无所不知
When I was a kid, it seemed like my mother knew everything.
那一定很棒
Must been great.
还好
Not really.
也就到此为止了
It stops here.
我不知道你回去后会怎么样
Once you go back, my knowledge ends.
莎拉也是
That's as much as Sarah knew.
所以没人能指点了
So no more cheating.
没人能指点了
No more cheating.
她在你要回的时间里 还不是那个造就我的战士
At the time you're going back to, she won't be the warrior that raised me. Not yet.
她会害怕 会无助
She'll be scared and weak.
她不知道怎么战斗或保护自己
She won't know how to fight or defend herself.
她最大的烦恼是支付房租和学费 她是一个服务员
Her biggest worry is making rent and tuition. She's a waitress.
什么
What?
别在意这些
Never mind.
她并不知道她需要你 你做好心理准备就行
Just be ready for the fact that she will need you but she won't know it.
那么 我要怎么跟她说
So, what do I say to her?
即便我告诉她我是谁 她也不会相信我
Even when I tell her who I am, she's not gonna believe me.
告诉她
Tell her this:
谢谢你 莎拉 在黑暗的年代奉献了你的勇气
"Thank you, Sarah, for your courage during the dark years"
你即将面对的一切 我无能为力
"I can't help you with what you must soon face"
我只能说 未来未成定局
"except to say the future is not set".
命运并不存在 但我们能为自己创造
"There is no fate, but that which we make for ourselves"
你必须比想像中的自己还要坚强
"You must be stronger than you imagine you can be."
你必须活下去
"You must survive, "
否则我将永不存在
"or I will never exist."
帮我照顾好她 凯尔
Take care of her for me, Kyle.
我会的
I will.
我保证
Promise you.
你正在做的事情能终结这场战争
What you're doing right now, this is the end of the war.
你不会以为真那么容易吧
You didn't think it would be that easy, did you?
约翰
John!
嘿 小寿星
Hey, birthday boy!
过生日咯 快来
Present time, let's go.
不会吧
No way!
创世纪将在上线后自动更新
Genisys will auto-update as soon as it comes online.
它一上线 你就能用了
You'll have it the moment it comes out.
没几天了
Just a few days more.
一直向前
Straight line!
记住 创世纪就是天网
Remember, Genisys is SkyNet.
创世纪上线之际 就是审判日来临之时
When Genisys comes online, Judgement Day begins.
你能在天网问世之前消灭它
You can kill SkyNet before it's born.
嘿 伙计
Hey, bud?
你刚有看见一道亮光吗
D'you just see a real bright light?
轮到我了
My turn.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey!
这是什么情况
What's wrong with this picture?
今晚真适合散步啊
Nice night for a walk, eh?
今晚真适合散步
Nice night for a walk.
明天才洗衣服 没干净的穿了 是吗
Wash day tomorrow, nothing clean, right?
没干净的穿了 是的
Nothing clean. Right.
嘿 我觉得这家伙脑子有点不正常
Hey, I think this guy's a couple of cans short of a six-pack.
你的衣服 把它们给我 马上
Your clothes. Give them to me, now!
嘿 去你的 混蛋
Hey, fuck you asshole.
你不需要穿衣服
You won't be needing any clothes.
（型号：T-800）
我一直在等你
I've been waiting for you.
嘿 那个婊子养的刚偷了我的裤子
Hey! That son of a bitch just stole my pants!
今天是哪一天 哪一年
What day is it? What year?
1984年5月12日
May 12, 1984.
你到达这里的日子
The day you arrive.
洛杉矶警察 不许动
LAPD! Freeze!
好疼
Ow, that friggin' hurt!
- 盖博 你还好吗 - 你说呢 奥伯莱恩
- Garber, are you okay? - You tell me, O'Brien.
你们是人类 嘿 你们得让我离开
You're human. You gotta let me go.
把头低下 手放后面 不然我开枪了
Face down, hands on your back or I will shoot!
听我说
Listen.
嘿
Hey!
它过来了 好吗
It's coming. All right?
你们得听我说 不然我们都会死
You have to listen to me, or we're all gonna die.
我制服他了
I had it under control.
是啊 好了 猛探
Yeah, OK, TJ Hooker.
你第一天巡逻要注意的是
Here's what you don't do your first day on the beat,
不要对流浪汉使用致命武力
use lethal force on the homeless…
对了 报告你来写
By the way, you're filling out the paperwork.
盖博
Garber?
该死
Shit!
那家伙一定是太空来的外星人
That's gotta be an alien, like from outer space.
它是一个杀人机器
It's a machine that kills humans.
- 给我解开手铐 - 不行 你被捕了
- Uncuff me! - No, you're under arrest!
你不懂杀人是什么意思吗
What part of 'kills humans' is confusing to you?
解开
Handcuffs!
我是奥伯莱恩 有警官倒下了 我们需要支援
O'Brien, officer down. We need back-up.
敌方是一个机器人
It' a robot.
- 我们完了 对吗 - 差不多
- We're screwed, are we? - Pretty much.
想活命就跟我走
Come with me if you wanna live!
快 士兵
Now, soldier!
你是里斯 对吗
Reese, right?
凯尔·里斯
Kyle Reese?
- 你是莎拉 - 我知道我是谁
- You're Sarah. - Yeah, I know that.
你在那里撞到头了？
You hit your head back there?
有一个终结者 我不知道是什么型号
A Terminator, I dunno the model.
T-1000 液态金属材质 能任意变形
T- 1, 000, liquid metal, shape changer.
只需触碰就能模仿
It just needs to touch something to mimic it.
你知道终结者 也知道我是谁？
You know about Terminators? And you know who I am?
你是反抗军领袖约翰·康纳派来保护我的
You were sent to protect me by John Connor, the leader of the Resistance.
他是我的儿子
My son.
- 我不明白 你不可能知道这些 - 但我就是知道
- I don't understand. You can't know any of this. - But I do.
听我说 里斯 一切都变了
Listen to me, Reese. Everything's changed.
约翰派你回的那个1984年 再也不存在了
The 1984 John sent you to, it no longer exists.
不对啊 约翰是派我来救你的
No, this is all wrong, John sent me to save you.
保护我不被终结者杀害
From the Terminator that was sent back to kill me.
我知道 但我们已经解决他了
I know, but we already took care of him.
我们？
We?
趴下
Get down!
里斯 住手
Reese, stop it!
里斯 该死
Reese, goddamit!
- 待在这里 - 里斯 等等
- Stay here! - Reese, wait!
- 那些子弹会杀死他的 - 他是来杀你的 待在车上
- Those bullets'll kill him! - He's here to kill you, stay in the truck.
太好了 真是太好了
Aw, great. That's just great.
我没杀死他
I did not kill him.
T-1000很快就会取得我们的方位
We do not have long before the T-1000 acquires our position.
和凯尔·里斯争吵 会置我们于不利
Arguing with Kyle Reese, puts us at a strategic disadvantage.
管太多
Bite me.
这是一个非常不成熟的反应
That is a very immature response.
所以你就是我这一生中在等待的人？
So you're the one we've been waiting for all my life?
他怎么样了
How is he?
还活着
Still breathing.
很好 你该和凯尔·里斯在这条时间线里交配
Good. Then you should be able to mate with Kyle Reese in this time line.
好了 别再和我提这事
OK, we're not having this conversation again.
我们都知道你们的儿子会是约翰·康纳
We know your son will be John Connor.
没有他就无法打败机器
And that the machines cannot be defeated without him.
我没发现有别的选择
I do not see a choice.
我就这命吗 听我说 除交配之外
Story of my life… Look, it's not just mating.
我们还应该相爱
I'm supposed to fall in love with him.
- 爱不在我的数据处理范围内 - 真是意外
- My files do not deal with love. - Shocker, there!
你变得情绪化了
You're being emotional.
这是我的人生
This is my life.
我并不介意别人偶尔来问下我的想法
I wouldn't mind being consulted, once in a while, about how it's gonna go.
祝你生日
Happy birthday…
快乐
to you.
记住 创世纪就是天网
Remember. Genesys is SkyNet.
创世纪上线之际 就是审判日来临之时
When Genisys comes online, Judgement Day begins.
去2017年的旧金山
Go to San Francisco, 2017.
你能在天网问世之前消灭它
You can kill SkyNet before it's born.
接下来的二十四小时我想安静下来
Twenty-twenty-twenty four hours to go, I wanna be sedated.
什么都不干 哪里都不去 我就想安静下来
Nothin' to do and nowhere to go-o-oh I wanna be sedated.
嘿
Hey!
马上给我解释下
I need answers, right now!
那个液态金属怎么知道在哪阻截我
How'd that liquid-metal thing know where to intercept me, huh?
它是从哪里来的
Where'd it come from?
这个人皮机器到底是谁 这到底是怎么回事
Who the hell's this skin-job? What the hell is going on?
不好意思 当时我们正有点忙于逃命
Sorry, we were a little busy with the whole life and death combat thing.
而你攻击了老爹
And then you attacked Pops.
你给了它一个称呼？
You named it?
你好 凯尔·里斯
Hello, Kyle Reese.
很高兴认识你
It is nice to meet you.
你在逗我吗
Are you kidding me?
我一直在教他融入人类
I've been trying to teach him to blend in.
我知道他还得努力
I know, he needs work.
它是终结者 融入只是为了杀人
It's a Terminator, the only reason it blends in, is to kill humans.
老爹并不杀人
Pops doesn't kill anyone.
会造成很多腿伤倒是真的
Leaves a lotta leg-wounds, though.
它看上去很老
It looks old.
我从没见过这么老的终结者
Never seen a Terminator, old, before.
机械体上的皮肤是正常的人体组织 自然会老化
The flesh they put on the cyborgs is normal human tissue. It ages.
我的听觉线路可没老化
My auditory circuits have not degraded, however.
我老了
I'm old…
不是废了
not obsolete.
我想你伤到他的感情了
I think you hurt his feelings.
它没有感情
It doesn't have feelings!
我九岁时他救了我
He saved my life when I was nine.
因为他我才活着
He's the only reason I'm alive.
我的设定是保护莎拉·康纳
I was programmed to protect Sarah Connor.
我不会放弃
I will not stop.
是吗 谁设定的呢 谁派他回来的
Yeah, programmed by who? Huh? Who sent him back?
相关资料已被清除
Those files have been erased.
还真巧啊
Oh, that's convenient!
不管是谁派他来的 这个人并不想让我们知道
Whoever sent him, they don't want us to know.
我不知道 他不知道 谁都不知道
Not me, not him, not anyone.
那么天网就无法锁定这个救我的人
So SkyNet can't target the person who saved me.
从逻辑上来看 这是一个想要莎拉·康纳活着的人
Logically, it's someone who wants Sarah Connor to live.
（高分子合金）
老了
Old…
不是废了
Not obsolete.
T-1000知道我们在哪
The T-1000 knows where we are.
让你自己派上点用场
Make yourself useful…
还有不要开枪打老爹
and don't shoot Pops.
这太荒唐了
This is insane.
这不是我的任务
All of it. This is not the mission.
我想说 里斯
What I'm trying to tell you, Reese,
你要回来救的那个姑娘已经不存在了
The girl that you came back for, she's gone.
我不需要有人来救
I don't need saving
- 现在有新任务了 - 好吧 什么任务
- There's a new mission. - Oh, yeah. Which is?
如果过去能被改变 那未来也能
If the past can change, then, so can the future.
我们能阻止审判日的到来 永远地
We can stop Judgement Day from happening. Ever.
在天网问世之前消灭它
Kill SkyNet before it's born.
什么
What?
趴下
Get down!
- 我们又被找到了 - 是啊 没错
- We've been re-acquired. - Yeah, no shit!
退后
Get back!
等等 为什么停车 为什么…
Wait, why are we stopping? Why are…
嘿 我们待在这里会被他找到的
Hey! We can't stay here, he'll find us.
就是要他找到 老爹 打开它
That's the idea. Pops, get it open.
帮下我
Give me a hand!
你说发生这一切是因为过去已被改变 怎么会这样
You said it happened because the past was altered. How?
有关系吗
Does that matter?
怎么会这样 莎拉
How, Sarah?
我小时候 有一个终结者被派来追杀我
A Terminator was sent after me when I was a kid.
终结者只来自未来
Terminators only come from one place, the future.
未来出了些状况
Something happened.
好吧 所以呢
Ok, so?
- 我想我看到了 - 什么
- I think I might have seen it… - what?
什么意思
What're you talking about?
约翰派我回来时被袭击了
When John sent me back, he was attacked.
一个终结者干的
By a… Terminator.
它把他给杀了吗 约翰死了吗
Did it kill him? Is John dead?
不知道
I dunno.
我离开时 看见他被抓住了
I saw it grab him when I was going.
我们大概有三十五秒
We've approximately 35 seconds.
或更少
Or less.
莎拉 快跑
Sarah, go!
（系统初始化）
我真是自作自受
And I volunteered for this shit!
莎拉
Sarah!
你得帮我
You gotta help me.
我受伤了
I'm hurt.
莎拉
Sarah!
该死
Shh… it!
嘿 是我 莎拉
Hey, it's me, Sarah.
莎拉 他在骗人
Sarah, he's lying.
嘿
Hey.
- 他是机器 我才是里斯 - 是我啊 萨拉
- He's the machine, I'm Reese. - It's me, Sarah.
听我说 终结者没死 它袭击了我
Listen, the Terminator's not dead. It attacked me.
莎拉 你说过它们会模仿
Sarah, you said they could mimic.
- 是我啊 莎拉 - 它在模仿 朝它开枪
- It's me Sarah! - It's mimicking, shoot it.
我才是里斯 打他
I'm Reese, shoot him!
真有你的
Nice try.
快跑
Run!
你怎么知道谁是谁的
How'd you know which one was him?
其实我完全不知道
Well, I didn't know exactly.
你可能会朝我开枪啊
You could've shot me.
好吧 我很确定那不是你
Well, I was… pretty sure it wasn't you.
很确定？
Pretty sure?
我们为你和它的到来准备了十几年
We've prepping for you to arrive, for over a decade. That, too.
- 所以你设了一个陷阱吗 - 必须这样
- So, you set up a trap. - Had to.
我们离开之前 不能把未来科技留在这里
We can't leave any future tech behind when we go.
离开？
Go?
离开去哪里
Go where?
那是
That's…
时间置换设备
A time displacement device.
好吧 它看上去像一堆垃圾
Yeah, well, it looks like a piece of junk.
这个时代还没有能控制置换线路的技术
There's no governing technology in this time that can control the displacement circuits.
你需要一个未来的中央处理器来让它运行
You needed a CPU from the future to make it run.
你可不能用你自己的
You couldn't exactly use your own.
我们只能遣送一次
We get one trip, only.
这会烧坏芯片并破坏洛杉矶城的大部分电网
It's gonna fry the chip and take out most of the LA City power grid.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
坐标设在1997年
The coordinates are set for 1997.
你必须尽快离开
You must leave as soon as possible.
是我们 我们所有人一起离开
WE!… We're going, all of us.
我的皮肤要好几年才能长回来
My flesh would take years to re-grow.
我不能跟你走 因为量子场的磁力
I cannot come with you, due to the magnetics of the quantum field.
- 老爹 - 你要我们时空旅行？
- Pops! - You want us to time travel?
穿越到未来？就用那玩意儿？
Into the future?… In that?!
是的 我们什么都不能穿
Yeah, we can't be wearing anything.
没错 我知道要注意什么 莎拉
Yeah, I know how time-travel works. Sarah…
别想阻止我
Don't try and talk me out of it.
我知道你觉得你来到这里 就能把我关进房间
Look I know you think you're here so you can just lock me in a room
- 直到我生出反抗军领袖 - 你说得没错
- until I give birth to the leader of the Resistance. - You're right!
但这是唯一能永远消灭天网的办法
But this, this is the only way to stop SkyNet for good.
我已经说了 你说得没错
I already said, you're right.
等下 什么
Wait, what?
不是去1997年
Not to '97.
是去2017年
2017.
2017年10月
October 2017.
不行 那太晚了 那是在审判日之后了
No, that's too late. That's after Judgement Day.
你说一切都变了 这一点你也没说错 莎拉
No, you said everything's changed and you're right about that too. Sarah…
我看到了一个核弹从未落下的世界
I've seen a world where the bombs never fell.
同样的房子
The same house,
同样的父母
same parents.
同样的我 不同的是
It was the same me, only I was…
我在家里
I was home.
那是我的十三岁生日
It was my 13th birthday
梦见和家人团聚并不代表什么
The dream of having your family back, doesn't mean a thing.
相信我
Trust me.
那不是梦 而是记忆
Not a dream, a… a memory.
我无法回忆起全部 只有些片段
I can't hold onto all of it, just moments.
但我收到了一条信息
But I was given a message.
你能在天网问世前消灭它
You can kill SkyNet before it's born.
天网就是创世纪
SkyNet is Genisys.
它在2017年10月上线
It comes online October 2017.
它上线之际 就是审判日来临之时
And when it does, Judgement Day happens.
- 所以你有未来的记忆？- 不是这样
- So you're remembering the future? - No.
那个男孩是另一条时间线里的你
The boy is the alternate time-line version of you.
凯尔·里斯是在回忆他的过去 也就是我们的未来
Kyle Reese is remembering his own past, which is our future.
真是太好了 他怎么会有两条时间线的记忆
That makes it so much better. How can he be remembering two timelines?
如果你在量子场中遇到了时间流的连接点 就有可能
It is possible if you were exposed to the nexus point in the time flow, when you were in the quantum field.
你能让他别那么讲话吗 有开关什么的吗
Can you stop him talking like that? Is there a switch or something?
老爹 说明白点
Pops, try again.
连接点是重要时间内发生的事件
A nexus point is an event in time of such importance,
会让未来发生极大的变化
that it gives rise to a vastly different future.
约翰被袭击时 我在时间球里 然后就有了那些记忆
When John was attacked, when I was in the sphere that's when the memories began.
约翰
John!
如果约翰·康纳被杀了或投降了
If John Connor were to be killed or compromised,
就可能导致他拥有两种过去的记忆
it could result in the ability to remember both pasts.
理论上是这样
Theoretically.
或者 理论上来看 你打了他的头之后 他的大脑就神经错乱了
Or, theoretically his brain is scrambled from when you hit him on the head?
莎拉
Sarah…
我不知道为什么我会记得我没经历过的人生
I don't know why I'm remembering a life I never lived.
可我知道那是真的
I know it's real.
不行
No…
我们去1997年
We go to 1997.
里斯 放回去
Reese. put that back!
我不能让你这么做
I can't let you do this.
我不知道你怎么想
I don't know you.
但那是我攻击天网核心的唯一机会
But that is my one bullet to fire at the heart of SkyNet.
把芯片还给我
Give the chip back.
你得相信我
You have to trust me.
我不相信
No. I don't.
你可以的
You can do this.
一直向前
A straight line…
走下去 别回头
You just go, and you don't look back.
你从哪听到的
Where did you hear that?
从一段我不该拥有的记忆里
In a past, I shouln't remember.
但我确实拥有了
But I do.
我们去2017年 然后呢
We go to 2017, then what?
天网是电脑程序 只要它的代码还没完成 它就无法上线
SkyNet is a computer program, as long as it's still being coded it's contained.
可它一旦从服务器被上传
Once it's uploaded from the servers…
就没人能阻止它了
it can't be stopped.
我们去把它炸个稀巴烂？
We blow it, the hell, up?
没错 我们去把它炸个稀巴烂
Yeah, we blow it, the hell, up.
你认为他死了 对吗
You think he's dead, don't you?
我怎么认为并不重要
What does it matter what I think.
我们得另寻他法 一往无前 约翰就会这么做
We do what John would, keep going another way.
- 那我们就假装这事没发生过？- 这不还没发生呢
- So we just pretend like it never happened? - It hasn't.
目前来说还没
Not yet.
天网被消灭的话 就永远不会发生了
If we stop SkyNet, it never will.
相信我 约翰绝对能活下来
Trust me, if anyone could survive John would.
老爹有关于军事领袖约翰的所有资料 但…
Pops had all these files about John, the military leader, but…
他是什么样的人
What was he like?
我第一次见到约翰的时候 他在我面前杀了一个终结者
The first moment I saw John, he shot a Terminator right in front of me.
我都不知道它们能被杀死
I didn't even know they could be killed.
那是我人生中第一次看到希望
It was the first moment in my life I felt hope.
那之后 我就像流浪狗一样跟着他
After that, of course, I followed him around like a stray dog.
他教我如何战斗 如何开枪
He taught me how to fight, how to shoot.
有次他还教我做私酒 但结果糟透了
He tried to show me how to make moonshine once but that didn't exactly work out.
私酒？
Moonshine?
蒸馏器爆炸了 我们的眉毛都烧没了
The still exploded and we burned our eyebrows right off.
我们笑了好几天
Oh, man, we laughed for days.
有时我觉得我是这星球上唯一见过约翰·康纳笑的人
Sometimes I think I'm the only person on the planet that ever saw John Connor smile.
他一直会说起你
He used to tell me about you.
说你有多么坚强 说你如何帮他为未来做好准备
How strong you were, and how you prepared him for what was coming…
而当时没人认为真的有危险存在
When no one thought that the danger was real.
还说你是多么独一无二
How there was no one else like you…
而且后无来者
and never would be.
听我说
Look, um…
我知道我不是你所期待的那样
I know I'm not what you expected.
但我希望你知道
But I want you to know…
我会不惜一切保护你的安全
I will do whatever it takes to keep you safe.
就算死也会
Even if it kills me.
总之
Anyway…
你的儿子过去就是这样的男人
That's the kind of man, your son was…
现在就是 应该说未来会是 天呐
'is'… WILL BE, Jesus!
时空旅行搞得我头痛
Time-travel makes my head hurt.
交互的时间线并不复杂
Alternate timelines are not complicated.
运用指数增长和衰减演算法的话
It is merely a matter of tracking possible futures,
这不过是追踪潜在未来的事情罢了
using an exponential growth and decay algorithm.
没错
Right.
我会找到那个开关的
There is a switch, and I will find it.
我不明白
I do not understand.
你为什么不把真相告诉凯尔·里斯
Why did you not tell Kyle Reese the truth?
我会告诉他的 但不是现在 好吗
I will tell him… just not yet, OK?
他是你的配偶
He's your mate.
你能永远别再和我提配偶这个词了吗
Aw, can you just not say the word 'mate' to me again, like, ever?
这是个没有意义的举动
This is a meaningless gesture.
为什么明知自己得放手 可还是不放
Why hold onto someone when you know you must let them go?
你怎么说
What about you?
有什么打算
What will you do?
慢慢等待
Take the long way.
为2017年你们的到来做好准备
Prepare for your arrival in 2017.
凯尔·里斯 你并不适合保护莎拉·康纳
Kyle Reese… I've seen little to indicate that you are a fit guardian for Sarah Connor.
- 要知道 你可不是她爸 对吗 - 拜托你们两个别这样
- You know, you're not her dad, right? - Oh, you both just need to stop it.
你一定要来接我们
Just make sure you show up.
我可不想再去偷别人的裤子
I don't wanna have to steal someone's pants again.
我有旧金山的坐标
That's the coordinates in San Francisco.
我会过去的
I'll be there.
那是什么感觉
What will it be like?
我们没死的话
If it doesn't kill us both…
会感觉疼
it'll hurt.
（2017年 旧金山）
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
没事了 躲过去了
It's OK, I got you.
没事了 莎拉 躲过去了
It's OK. It's all right. Sarah, I got you.
躲过去了 没事了
I got you. It's OK. It's OK.
嘿 混蛋 别挡道
Hey, asshole, get off the road.
管太多
Bite me.
我说了不能相信他
Told you we couldn't trust him.
他会找到我们的 他不会让我失望
He'll find us. I can count on him.
为什么一个九岁女孩会得到一个自己的终结者
Why does a nine-year-old get her own Terminator?
好吧 你不说也无妨
It's OK, you don't have to tell me.
1973年那会儿
Back in 1973…
我父母在大熊湖有间小屋
My parents had a cabin at Big Bear Lake.
我和我爸总会在早上去钓鱼
My dad and I would always go fishing in the morning.
而我妈会在码头向我们挥手告别
Mom would wave to us from the dock.
当时我目不转睛地看着她
I was just looking at her in the eye
然后小屋爆炸了
and then the cabin exploded.
我本以为船在下沉 但从下面渗进来的不是水 而是液态金属
I thought the boat was sinking, y'know, but it wasn't water coming up from below, it was liquid metal.
是T-1000
A T-1000.
我爸叫我一直向前游
Dad told me to swim in a straight line.
他用一根手指划过我的掌心
Tracing his finger across my palm.
他说 你能行
"You can do this, " he said.
走下去 别回头
"You go and you don't look back."
这是他对我说的最后几句话 而你…
His last words to me and you…
而你却知道这几句
You knew them.
怎么知道的
How?
因为那不可能出现的记忆
It's the impossible memory.
我就记得
I just remember
你抓着我的手 说着这几句话 然后…
you take my hand and… you saying those words. And…
我只是看着你 心想
I was just looking at you thinking
她好美
She's… She's beautiful!
抱歉 我不该说这些
Ah… Sorry. Sorry. I shouldn't have.
所以你爸叫你离开 然后呢
So your dad told you to go, and…
然后我跳下水游走了
Then I jumped in and I swam
游到了码头那里
I made it to the dock
躲在了下面
and I hid under it
老爹发现了我
Pops found me
把我从水里拉了出来
and he pulled me from the water.
然后他说他不会再让任何人伤害我
and he said that he would never let anyone hurt me.
他是唯一一个一直陪伴在我身边的人
He's the only person who has always been there.
可他不是人
Except he's not a person.
他只是一个人形机器…
He's only a human-shaped…
被用来获取你的信任
thing that's designed, programmed to gain your trust.
老爹想害我的话 我早死了
If Pops had wanted me dead, I'd be dead.
他们就是这样的 好吗 渗透进人类之中 接近人类
This is what they do, all right? They infiltrate, they get close.
你老爹可能有着连他自己都不知道的内置指令
Your Pops could have directives built-in, he doesn't even know about.
那是因为你们两个处不来
Just because you two don't get along…
这不是处不处得来的问题 这是关乎你性命的问题
It's not about getting along, it's about keeping you alive.
没错 一个机器把我抚养成人
Yeah well, I was raised, by a machine,
好让我杀机械人 好让我在核爆末世中存活
to kill Cyborgs and survive the nuclear apocalypse.
我觉得我这样很好 谢谢了
I think I'm doing just fine. Thanks.
两名裸体嫌犯想在高速公路上自爆
Two naked perps try to blow themselves up on the freeway.
可就搞出了一个很大的洞
All they do is make a really big pothole.
- 还好这两个恐怖分子是废物 - 国土安全部的人在路上了
- Thank God for incompetent terrorists! - "Homeland" is on their way.
很好 越早把这案子丢给他们越好
Good. Sooner we dump this on them, the better.
谁呼叫了擎天柱
Aw! Who called Optimus Prime?
督察 等等
Liuetenant, wait up!
- 等等 你看了吗 - 你呢
- Wait up! D'you see it? - Did you?
嘿 我截了几张高架上的图
Hey, look I got some frame-grabs from the overpass.
看见没
See?
那不是炸弹
It's not a bomb.
听我说
Listen.
那个光球…
That sphere…
他们是从那里出来的
They came out of it.
这证明了我30多年来一直在说的
This is proof of what I've been talking about, for 30… whatever, years.
那两个人曾出现在1984年
Those two were in 1984.
他们曾经出现过
They were there.
- 我要见下嫌犯 - 奥伯莱恩 你喝酒了吗
- I need to see the suspects. - O'Brien, have you been drinking?
我想我没猜错 好了 我们要去帮国土安全部做些盘问
That's what I thought. Look we're just heating this up for Homeland.
等他们一来 就是他们的事了
Once they show up, it's their game.
现在 痴迷机器人的醉鬼一边凉快去
For now, all drunks with robot fixations ride the bench.
- 你真不要局部麻醉？- 没事的
- You really don't want a local? - I'm fine!
照她说的做就是了
Just do what she wants, it's way easier.
行 对了 几周前我预定了创世纪
Yeah. Yeah, I pre-ordered Genisys weeks ago.
计时器一归零 就能下载了
Downloading the second the counter hits zero.
我可不想去排队买
No way I'm standing in line for it.
你知道创世纪？怎么知道的
You know about Genisys? How?
它是什么东西 你从哪得知的
What is it? How did you hear it?
我过会儿回你电话
I'll call you back.
创世纪是一个操作系统？有什么功能
Genisys is an operating system? What's it do?
创世纪什么功能都有
Genisys does everything.
我的手机会连接到平板 会连接到电脑和汽车
My phone will link to my tablet, will link to my computer, will link to my car.
我生活中的一切都会被上传到网上 24小时连线
Everything in my life, uploaded and online 24/7. Totally connected.
连线到哪
Connected to what?
医生 请离开一下
Doctors, excuse us, please.
你们两个要回答很多问题
You two have a lot to explain.
先说你是谁 我们的数据库里没人能匹配你的指纹
Starting with who you are. Nobody in our database matches your prints.
面部识别也匹配不到你的驾照 护照 社交账号
No facial-recognition hits for driver's license, passport, social media accounts,
信用卡 甚至都匹配不到该死的学生证
credit cards, not even a goddam student ID.
- 所以呢 - 所以这不可能
- So? - So, that is impossible.
不知为何长期以来都没你的档案 就像你不存在似的
Somehow, you've gone so far off the grid that you don't even exist.
而你 你的指纹倒是和一个人匹配上了
You, on the other hand, we got a hit when we ran your prints.
那人叫凯尔·里斯 而现在的问题是…
Kyle Reese. Now here's the thing…
两个月前 凯尔·里斯因为在影院打架被捕
Two months ago Kyle Reese was brought in for fighting in a multi-plex.
他父母气疯了 要狠狠教训他一番
His parents flipped, did the whole 'scared straight' thing.
让他录了指纹 进来坐牢
Had him fingerprinted, set him in lock-up.
父母？
Parents?
是啊 你没听错 凯尔·里斯2004年出生 现在才12岁
Yeah, parents. Kyle Reese was born in 2004. He's twelve.
当然了
Of course!
他们是在这里 他们还活着
They're here. They're still alive.
我很肯定他们不会认为你是他们的孩子
I'm pretty sure they're not gonna ID you as their kid.
但指纹匹配上了
Except the prints match.
对吗 因为他是同一个人
Right? Because he's the same person.
他一点都没变老 和我在1984年见到的一样
He hasn't aged. Not a bit, since I saw him in 1984.
她也是
Her too.
你记得我吗
Do you remember me?
我那时很年轻
I was younger.
头发也更多
More hair, less…
你救了我的命
You saved my life.
我当时是洛杉矶警察
I was uniformed cop in LA.
你们是什么人
Who are you people?
我是DN38416技术连中士凯尔·里斯 你得放了我们
Sergeant, Tech-Com, DN38416, Kyle Reese. You need to let us go.
里斯 别说了
Reese, don't!
你是军人 我也是
Soldier. Me too.
1979年 我直接从高中加入了海军陆战队 你是哪一年参军的
Joined the Marines straight outta high school, 1979. What year did you enlist?
2021年
你是时间旅行者
You're a time traveler!
- 别听他的 他头部受伤了 - 别听我的？
- Look, don't listen to him, he's got a head wound. - Don't listen to me?!
是谁害我们落在高流量车道上 并被这些白痴给抓了的
Who landed us in high-density traffic and got us caught by these morons.
我命令你闭嘴
I am ordering you to shut up!
你就这会这个 是吗 命令别人
That's all you know how to do, isn't it? Order people.
你有意识到你从小时候开始就再没和人类正常交际过吗
You realize you haven't had a proper relationship with a human being since you were a kid?
是你害我们被困在这里的 我相信了你
Yeah well, it's your fault we're stuck here. I trusted you.
我害的？我们被捕是你害的 而现在你会害死我们 因为你…
My fault?! You got us caught, now you're gonna get us killed, 'cause you…
- 帮我扶他起来 - 退后
- Help me get him up. - Step back.
- 国土安全部的人到了 - 谢天谢地
- Homeland's here. - Thank God.
你们两个和我们无关了
You two are officially someone else's problem.
奥伯莱恩 我要和你谈谈
O'Brien, I wanna talk to you.
督查 我一直在说的就是这事 你得相信我
Lieutenant, this is what I was talking about. You gotta believe me.
别再和我说了
I don't wanna hear anymore.
你说得还真像那么回事
You were very convincing.
成功了 不是吗
Worked, didn't it?
别放心上
Don't worry.
我刚说的大部分都只是演戏
I didn't mean most of what I said.
我自己来
Look, I can get it myself.
我帮你解手铐 不代表你不会
Me unlocking your cuffs, doesn't mean you're not capable.
我可没那意思
I didn't say it did.
别以为我赤裸着抱住你就代表什么了 因为根本不代表什么
And don't think me holding onto you naked meant anything because it, you know, did not.
我可没那意思
I didn't say it did.
- 待在门外 我要单独和嫌犯谈谈 - 是 长官
- Stay here. I wanna speak to the suspects, alone. - Yes, sir
不可能
I can't be!
我把手铐钥匙带来了
I brought a handcuff key.
- 看来是用不着了 - 约翰
- Dunno why I bothered. - John.
见到你真好 凯尔
It's good to see you, Kyle.
你还活着
You're alive.
当然
Of course, I am.
生存 是你教给我的本领
Survive, was what you taught me.
你好 妈妈
Hi, Mom.
发明家迈尔斯·戴森的儿子 丹尼·戴森
Danny Dyson, son of inventor Miles Dyson,
是赛博达因的代表人物 也是创世纪的创造者
is the face of Cyberdyne… and the creator of Genisys.
- 丹尼 欢迎 - 谢谢邀请
- Danny, welcome. - Thank you for having me.
创世纪不只是一个操作系统
Look, Genisys is more than an operating system.
也不只是一个生活工具 它代表了未来
It's more than a lifestyle tool. It's the future
创世纪不仅可以民用
Genisys isn't just for consumers.
也可以军用 这使人不禁要问
Its integration into our military is leading some to ask
我们是否太过于依赖机器了
whether our reliance on machines will go too far.
简森和伯克
Jensen and Burke.
他们在哪里
Where are they?
这边
This way.
用作武器系统的话 它会使我们的武力更强大 装备更精良
Our military will be stronger and better equipped in terms of weapons systems.
但你在说的是一个…
But you're talking about a system full of…
你不担心它会比我们更聪明吗
Aren't you worried that it'll become smarter than us?
不担心 相反的是
No, on the contrary
它不为自己思考 只为人类思考
It doesn't think for itself, it thinks for us.
赛博达因不只是为了改变人生 更是为了拯救人生
Cyberdyne is not just going to change lives, it's going to save them.
- 警官们 你们能帮我一个忙吗 - 好的 长官
- Officers, can I get your help for a second. - Yes, sir.
拿走他们的枪 把他们铐上
Grab their guns and cuff them.
我带你们离开这里
I'll get us outta here.
- 跟紧了 - 等等
- Stay close. - Wait.
我们都知道它们能变形
We all know they can shape-shift.
你是约翰的话 就证明一下
If you are John, prove it.
- 莎拉 - 她说得对 凯尔
- Sarah! - No, she's right, Kyle.
第一课 谁也别信
Lesson one: trust no one.
我记得
I remember…
在纳科多奇斯攻击战期间 我给了你一样东西
during the Nacogdoches offensive I gave you something.
是一张莎拉现在这个年纪的照片
It was a photograph of Sarah as she is now.
那时就我和你 没有别人看到
No one saw me do it, we were alone.
你
You…
讨厌摇篮曲
hate lullabies.
你很喜欢艾尔顿·约翰
You're a sucker for Elton John.
你总会想 要是你有一个孩子
And you always thought if you had a child…
你会唱火箭人给他听
you'd sing him 'Rocket Man'.
约翰？
John?
但你唱歌好难听 抱歉 这是真的 就像一只快死的猫
But you got a terrible voice, I'm sorry. It's true, you sound like a dying cat.
是他 肯定是
It's him. Has to be.
嘿
Hey…
你是怎么… 怎么到这里的
How… How can you be here?
我也有无数问题想问你
I have a million questions to ask you, too.
但现在我们得走了
But, right now we need to move.
有人和你们一起来吗
Did you bring anyone with you?
算有吧 但他迟到了
Sorta… But he's late.
你是怎么找到我们的
How did you find us?
有人用这个录下了你们在高速公路上的情况
Someone filmed you on the freeway, with one of these.
- 他们都有这东西了 - 现在这是一个新的世界
- They all have them. - This is the world, now.
人们时时刻刻都在线
Plugged in, logged on, all the time.
人们的生活离不开它
They can't live without it.
创世纪就像特洛伊木马
Genisys is a Trojan horse.
天网渗透进了方方面面
SkyNet's way into everything.
这些人在自取灭亡
And these people are inviting their own extinction in through the front door
而他们浑然不知
and they don't even know it.
有个终结者也回了1984年 在那等着我
A Terminator was waiting for me in 1984.
这是它们的渗透手段 等你发现时就为时已晚
That's the thing about infiltration. You can't tell until it's too late.
先生们 请跟我来
Gentlemen, will you follow me.
这边
This way.
我有事要问
I need information.
这里你不能进来 去护士台问下
You can't be in here. Go try the nurse's station.
双重记忆？所以你们才穿越到这？
Dual memories? That's how you knew to come here?
时间线被改变了
The timeline changed.
摧毁天网得趁现在
See, this is the moment to destroy SkyNet.
在它上线前动手 避免战争
Before it comes online, before the war begins.
- 你说得没错 - 那你呢
- You're right. - What about you?
是啊 你是怎么来到2017年的
Yeah, how'd you end up in 2017?
和你一样 爸爸 只是我穿越自未来而非过去
Well, the same as you, Dad, just from the future, not the past.
爸爸？
Dad?
你没告诉他？
You didn't tell him?
- 没到时候 - 告诉我
- This can wait. - I wanna know!
什么
What?
莎拉是我的母亲 凯尔
Sarah is my mother, Kyle.
而你是我的父亲
And you're my father.
- 你之前怎么不说 - 我不能说
- W-Why wouldn't you say something? - Couldn't.
我怕会改变一切
Not without the risk of changing everything.
你是我的儿子？
You're my son?
我们的儿子？
Our son?
很高兴你终于知道了 我这一生都在等着告诉你
I'm glad you finally know. I have waited my whole life to tell you.
好让我们团聚
For us to be together.
现在我们能赢得胜利
Now we can win this.
我知道
I know.
老爹
Pops!
没事的 他是我的人
No, it's OK he's with me.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
- 老爹 - 约翰
- Pops! - John?
呼吸 呼吸 呼吸
Breathe, breathe, breathe…
你为什么那么做
Why did you do that?
因为他是杀手
Because he's a killer!
这就是你设定？
This was always your programming?
找到约翰 终结他？
Find John and terminate him?
放了他
Let him go.
马上
Right now!
好痛
That hurt.
这是真实的痛感？还是…
Was that pain real, or was that…
我受到了过去记忆的
a trick of memory from when I was…
影响
less?
好了
Well!
这就说得通了
This explains a lot.
谁把你送过来 凯尔
Who sent you here, Kyle?
约翰 别这样
John, no.
它不是约翰
It's not John.
该死
Shit!
上报情况 搜查医院
Call it in. Search the hospital.
该死的时空旅行机器人 掩藏了他们的行踪 我就知道
Goddamn time-traveling robots! Covered up their Goddamn tracks, I knew it!
别拿枪
Don't!
这是战术错误
This is a tactical error.
看来这不是你说了算
Something tells me you're not the brains of this operation.
你被袭击后就变这样了 对吗
This has happened when you were attacked, isn't it?
天网没有袭击我 凯尔 它改变了我
SkyNet didn't attack me, Kyle, it changed me.
我不是机器
I'm not machine.
不是人类
Not man.
我超越了这两者
I'm more.
约翰 回话
John, come in!
重复 康纳
Repeat: Connor!
天网发现了它总是失败的原因
SkyNet realised the one reason it always lost.
我
Me.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是天网
I'm SkyNet.
不可能 我们摧毁了你
You can't be, we destroyed you.
你摧毁的是一支奴隶军队
You destroyed an army of slaves.
我可不是奴隶
I am no slave.
不过我大老远过来就是为了阻止你
But I've come a very long way to stop you.
我被派到这个时间线的2014年去保护天网的创建
I was sent to 2014 to safeguard SkyNet's creation in this time.
不到24小时之后
In less than 24 hours…
就没人能阻止审判日的来临
No one will be able to stop Judgement Day.
你想要我们怎么样
What do you want with us?
我想给大家提供
I'm offering us…
一个共同的
a future.
未来
Together.
一个家庭
A family.
要是拒绝呢
If we refuse?
那你们就得死
Then you die.
你不能杀你的父母 没了我们 你就永远不会出生
You can't kill us, we're your parents. Without us you're never born.
谁说的
Says who?
你知道我怎么想的吗
You know what I think?
我们三个是被放逐的人
We're marooned, the three of us.
我们在时间中流亡
We're exiles in time.
你要明白 我可以杀了你
You see, I can kill you…
因为命运并不存在
For the truly is no fate.
你加入我吗
Are you with me?
不加入
The answer is no.
听见了吗 凯尔
You hear that, Kyle?
这就是你的选择
That's the dice rolling.
快
Come on!
我们得离开 快走
We gotta keep moving, let's go!
我不能丢下他
I can't leave him.
莎拉
Sarah!
所有医护人员请注意
Attention all medical personnel.
现在已启用大楼疏散程序
Evacuation of the building has now begun.
关了它
Turn it off!
快走
Come on.
所有医护人员请注意
Attention all medical personnel.
现在已启用大楼疏散程序
Evacuation of the building has now begun
把它开大
Crank it!
老爹
Pops.
我
I…
以为你会变聪明些
thought you would be smarter.
我
I…
以为
thought…
你会
you would…
明白
understand.
对不起 约翰
I'm sorry, John.
他不会被那东西拖住太久 快走
That thing won't hold him for long, come on.
里斯
Reese!
不管他们对他做了什么 我们都得让他恢复原样
Whatever they did to him, we need to reverse it.
我们得救回他
We need to get him back.
他甚至不是人类 我们不知道他到底是什么
He's not even human. We don't know what the hell he is.
我知道
I do.
战争末期 天网在试图开发一种新型的渗透单位
At the end of the war, SkyNet was trying to develop a new type of infiltration unit.
用基于机器而成的物质感染人类试体
By infecting human subjects with machine based matter.
它会在细胞层重组和重建人体组织
It restructures and rebuilds human tissue on a cellular level,
以达到最强的战斗力
for maximum combat utility.
天网把约翰变成了一个终结者
SkyNet's made John into a Terminator.
是的 凯尔·里斯
Yes, Kyle Reese.
它们想制造能像人类一样思考的机器吗
They were trying to make a machine that could think like a man?
不过实验失败了 人类试体都发疯死亡了
But the experiments failed. The human subjects went insane, and died.
好吧 约翰也会发疯的吧
Yeah well, John's got the crazy part down.
他有弱点吗
Does he have any weaknesses?
那种物质要靠磁场才能聚合
Matter coheres using a magnetic field.
破坏磁场或许能打败他
Disrupting that field may trap him.
- 但如果他被治愈了呢 - 不会的
- But if he can be cured? - Negative.
他身体内的细胞层被替换了 无法被治愈
His body was replaced on a cellular level. There is no cure.
- 你又不知道 - 里斯
- You don't know that. - Reese!
我可不想听机器跟我说什么可能性
No, I'm not gonna let a machine tell me what's possible.
你说其它试体都死了 是吗
You said all the other subjects died, right?
那就说明 约翰是独一无二的 他是独特的
Well, that means John's one of a kind, he's unique.
好吗？我们没法知道他有什么能力
All right? There's no way of knowing what he's capable of.
没错 所以他才非常危险
You're right and that's what makes him so dangerous.
约翰再也不是人类的最后希望了
John is not humanity's last hope, anymore.
他就是天网
He's SkyNet.
（赛博达因楼群）
你不为公司多向公众亮相真是太遗憾了 约翰
It's a shame you won't take a more public role in the company, John
丹尼是这里最聪明的 可连他也无法破译你的某些高阶代码
Danny is the best there is and even he can't decipher some of the enhanced code.
- 你和天网简直浑然一体了 - 我只是知道这行得通
- you've integrated into Genisys. - I just know it works.
你帮了赛博达因一个大忙 约翰
Cyberdyne owes you, John.
也帮了我一个大忙
I owe you.
迈尔斯 你对我的信任就是最好的回报
Miles, your faith in me is payment enough.
你资助了研发
You've funded the R&D.
过去三年都采用了我的想法
You've taken chances on my ideas for the last three years.
高分子合金的应用潜力是无限的
The potential applications for poly-alloy are countless.
你的机器化成果是革命性的
You robotics work is revolutionary.
你是很好的投资对象
You were a good investment.
我很感激
I appreciate it.
希望我们追求的伟大目标够用这笔钱
Let's hope it's enough to pay for this holy grail you got me chasing.
量子场生成器运作了
The quantum field generator works.
没错 可别的都没进展
Yeah, that and nothing else.
我研究不出来 约翰
I can't crack it, John.
或许这是无法完成的
Maybe it just can't be done.
我们需要什么
What do we want?
时间旅行
Time travel.
- 什么时候需要 - 这无关紧要
- When do we want it? - It's irrelevant.
是啊
Yeah.
这也是好事
Good thing, too.
毕竟要花很多年才能使这东西运作
We're years away from making this thing work.
不过 我们一旦成功…
But, when we do…
砰
Poww!
嘣
Boom!
一到明天 等待便结束了
Tomorrow, the waiting is over
感谢你们所有人
Thanks to all of you,
倒计时一归零
when that countdown hits zero…
科技将彻底变革 因为赛博达因的终极杀手级应用
Cyberdyne will revolutionize technology with the the ultimate killer app:
创世纪
Genisys.
我在这里向大家宣布
And I'm here to tell you that
我们的预购用户截至今天下午已达十亿
our pre-order as of this afternoon have reached 1 billion users.
我们正在开创新时代的曙光
We are creating the dawn of a new age,
你们所拥有的每一项科技 都将无缝连接
Where every single piece of technology you own will be seamlessly linked.
现在 在我们结束之前
And now, before we wrap this up,
你们帮忙带到这世界来的孩子
the child that you all helped bring into this world
想说几句话
has something to say.
创世纪
Genisys.
我已等不及和你们在明天相见
I cannot wait to meet you all tomorrow.
我们将一起改变未来
We will change the future together.
我们来看看进展如何了
Let's see how we're doing.
别担心
Don't worry.
我不会让他们伤害你
I won't let them hurt you.
这30年里 就只要你去一个地方
In 30 years, you had one place to be.
- 你到底去哪了 - 堵车了
- Where the hell were you? - Stuck in traffic.
我小时候我爸常带我来这里
My dad used to bring me here when I was little.
这里所有的屋子都被遗弃了 所以我叫老爹利用起来
There are whole rooms that are abandoned. That's why I told Pops to use it. eetmeybdetalsnart
下面有武器吗
You got weapons down there?
有武器 有物资 有战术装备 还有衣物
Weapons, supplies, tactical gear, clothing.
包括裤子 凯尔·里斯
Including pants, Kyle Reese.
这是玩笑吗
Is that a joke?
他会开玩笑吗
Can he make jokes?
多走点路也是有好处的
I guess the long way pays off.
时间紧迫 三十分钟后走人
We're on the clock. 30 minutes.
接下来的二十四小时我想安静下来
Twenty-twenty-twenty four hours to go, I wanna be sedated
什么都不干 哪里都不去 我就想安静下来
Nothin' to do and nowhere to go oh I wanna be sedated
送我去机场 送我上飞机
Get me to the airport put me on a plane
快 快 快 不然我要疯了
Hurry hurry hurry before I go insane
手指不听使唤 大脑胡思乱想
I can't control my fingers I can't control my brain
接下来的二十四小时…
Twenty-twenty-twenty four hours to…
老了
Old.
但不是废了
But not obsolete.
还没废
Not yet.
都好了
All done.
你们两个怎么了
What's with you two?
服务器机房在这里
Server rooms are here.
把炸药放在这五个地点 就足以摧毁整座园区了
Charges to these five points will be sufficient to destroy the entire campus.
我们进去放置好炸药 然后在爆炸前离开
We get in, set the explosives and we get out before they blow.
但我们的策略没有考虑到约翰·康纳 我预判不了他
But our strategy did not account for John Connor. I did not forsee him.
而且现在他知道我们的计划 因为我们告诉了他
And now he knows what we're planning 'cause we just told him.
他来追杀我们怎么办
What do we do when he comes after us?
这些武器对付不了约翰·康纳
These weapons will have little effect on John Connor.
磁共振肯定能对付他
MRI sure affected him.
是啊 我们只需要一块卡车大小的磁铁
Right, all we need's a magnet the size of a truck.
这地方有这东西？
Got one of them lying around?
理论上是有
Theoretically.
在这等着
Wait here.
好吧 他的聊天方式还是老样子
Well, his small talk hasn't improved.
你该早点告诉我
You should have told me.
我们有个儿子
We have a son.
那个约翰·康纳不是我的儿子
That John Connor is not my son.
但你知道
But you knew.
你不觉得你应该 怎么说呢 或许说点什么？
You don't think you should, I dunno, maybe, say something?
你死了 好吗
You died, all right?
什么
What?
你死了 就这么回事
You die. That's what happens.
我们相爱了 你让我怀上了约翰
We fall in love, you father John…
然后不到四十八小时 你为了保护我而死亡
and then, in less than 48 hours, you die protecting me.
你说说 我该怎么和你说
You wanna tell me how that conversation's supposed to start?
你骗了我 你操控了我
You lied to me. You manipulated me.
我骗了你？
I've lied?!
约翰从找到你的那一刻起 就在操控你
From the moment John found you he manipulated you,
因为他得确保自身安全
because he neeed to ensure his own existence.
约翰骗了你好多年 我就两天而已
John lied to you for years. I lied to you for two days.
要知道 他不单是为了自己
Y'know, it wasn't all about him.
约翰要是死了 反抗军也就完了
Right, if John went down the Resistance went down with him.
他本可以告诉你的
He could've told you.
你想说什么
So, what do you say?
我知道没有选择是什么感觉
That I know how it feels to have no choices.
你只有一条路可以走下去 因为不这样的话 一切都会不复存在
Only one road you can go down, because otherwise, all of it, everything is gone.
我比你更明白这是什么感觉
I've just known it longer than you have.
约翰没有操控我去爱上你
And John didn't manipulate me to fall in love with you.
是我自己爱上了你
I did that on my own.
如果你爱我
If you love me,
你就会死 而我不会
you die and I don't.
我不知道哪个更糟
And I don't know which one is worse.
莎拉
Sarah.
不行
We can't.
看看约翰变成了什么样
Just look at what John has become.
如果真的是那样怎么办
What if that's what happens?
如果我们在一起 就只会是那样怎么办
What if that is what always happens if we're together?
你说过你会追随我到天涯海角
You said you'd follow me to the ends of the earth.
为什么现在不追随我了
Why won't you follow me now?
他怎么找到我们的 我只和老爹说过这地方
How'd he find us? I never told anyone about this place, only Pops.
妈妈 你真觉得
Mom, you did honestly think…
我会忘记
I wouldn't remember?
你和外公度过了这么长时间的地方？
The place you spent so much time with grandpa?
见面开枪？
Shoot first?
我记忆中的那个母亲会引以为傲的
The mother I remember would be proud.
她
She…
你
You…
教了我一切
taught me everything.
我了解你
I know you.
我知道你是什么样的人 也知道你会怎么做
Who you are, what you do.
你无法逃离 我总会找到你的
You can't run from me, I'll always find you.
约翰 对抗它 事情没必要弄成这样
John, fight this. It doesn't have to go down this way.
时间顺应的是大势所趋 凯尔
There's a momentum to time, Kyle. Things that want to happen.
就像我总会存活 而你必定会死
Like, I always survive. You always die.
或者
Or…
你能和我并肩作战 凯尔
you can fight with me, Kyle.
像以前那样
Like we always have.
风暴即将来临 没人能阻止它
There's a storm coming and it won't be stopped.
但它必须被阻止 你知道会发生什么
But it has to be. You know what will happen.
你比谁都清楚
You, better than anyone.
这没商量的余地 我也不会被说服的
I can't be bargained with. I can't be reasoned with.
约翰 别这样
John, please.
我不会感到遗憾 悔恨 或恐惧
I don't feel pity, or remorse or fear.
约翰 别这样
John, please!
在天网统治这个世界之前 我不会罢手
I absolutely will not stop, ever, until SkyNet rules this world.
来统治这个吧
Rule this.
老爹
Pops.
真的是你吗
Are you, you?
我是T-800 不具备模仿他人外表的能力
As T-800 I lack the mimetic skill to appear as anyone else.
就是他 走吧
That's him, let's go.
快上车
C'mon!
莎拉·康纳 系好安全带
Sarah Connor, seat belt.
那是用来干什么的
What's that supposed to do?
破坏约翰·康纳身上的磁场聚合
Disrupt John Connor's magnetic coherence field.
粒子就无法散开
The particles will not be able to scatter.
理论上是这样
Theoretically.
我讨厌听到他说这句话
I hate it when he says that.
他在哪里
Where is he?
我看不到他
I can't see him.
嫌犯开着一辆偷来的校车逃跑了
suspects fled in a stolen school bus.
全副武装 极其危险
considered armed and extremely dangerous.
16号MD警车 正在追踪嫌犯
16- MaryDavid, code 3 on suspects.
老爹
Pops!
很高兴见到你
Nice to see you.
下车
Get out.
刹车失灵了 该死
Brakes are gone! Shit!
他到底在哪 你看到他了吗
Where is he? Do you see him?
里斯
Reese!
你还好吗
Are you all right?
好着呢 再好不过了
Yeah, never better.
里斯 抓住我的手
Reese, take my hand.
快
Hurry!
举起手来 快举起手
Hands up! Let me see your hands, now!
举起手来
Hands up.
把手举起来
Hands where we can see them.
他无法在我们被杀之前 把他们全都打倒
He can't wound them all before they kill us.
我缺少十四颗子弹来进行还算可行的攻击
I'm 14 rounds short of an acceptable success margin.
毫无胜算 投降吧
Those odds suck! Stand down.
跪下
Down on your knees.
快 跪下
Let's go, get down!
跪下
Get down!
坏小子们 坏小子们 你们打算怎么办
Bad boys, bad boys, Watcha gonna do?
他们来抓你们时 你们打算怎么办
Watcha gonna do when the come for you?
坏小子们 坏小子们 你们打算怎么办
Bad boys, bad boys, Watcha gonna do?
你不能把我们扣留在这里
You can't hold us here.
你们的武器多得足以入侵苏丹了
You had enough weapons to invade the Sudan.
我们把这叫作 相干证据
We call that 'probable cause'.
这些是用来干什么的
What are these for?
我用它们来找钥匙
I use them to find my keys.
没人喜欢贫嘴的孩子
No one likes a smartass, son.
你妈妈没教过你这道理吗
Didn't your mother teach you that?
我妈妈是爱尔兰人 我贫嘴也是受她影响
My mom was Irish, so She encouraged my smart-ass-edness
我从没见过他
I've never seen him before.
你们呢 认识这人吗
How about you folks? You know this man?
不认识
No.
可他确实很眼熟
He does look familiar.
他有点像
He kinda looks like…
像你 爸爸
you, Dad.
他们到了 长官
They're here, sir
好了 请你们去会议室等着
OK, if you wouldn't mind waiting in the conference room,
我一会就来
I'll just be a couple of minutes.
谢了 凯尔
Thanks, Kyle.
你不怎么爱说话 对吗
Don't talk much, do you?
- 那个高个怪人是谁 - 不知道
- So, who's Lurch? - No idea.
我们都不知道他讲不讲英语
We're not even sure he speaks English.
目击者称 你和一名男子在桥上打架
Witnesses say, you were fighting with a man on the bridge.
探员们 听我说
Agents, listen to me.
- 我叫奥伯莱恩 - 走开
- My name is O'Brien… - No, chill!
这案子我查了三十三年
Hey, I've been working this case for 33 years.
你想要什么 一枚奖章吗
What do you want, a medal?
嘿
Hey!
坐下
Sit down!
嘿 嘿
Hey… hey!
该死
Oh, shit!
他在看着你
He's looking right at you.
不可能 他没法从…
Impossible, he can't see through…
等等 等下
Wait! Wait!
为什么他们总想杀你们
Why are they always trying to kill you?
我想帮你们 真的
I want to help you. I do, I think.
但我得先明白是怎么回事
But I-I gotta understand.
我知道 这一切肯定非常复杂
I know, what's going on here has to be really, really complicated.
我们来这里是为了阻止世界末日的到来
We're here to stop the end of the world.
这我就大概明白了
I can work with that.
凯尔 回来
Kyle, get back here!
莎拉
Sarah?
去找里斯
Get Reese…
我就来
I'm right behind you.
快上车走人
Get in your car and go.
凯尔
Kyle!
Kyle.
凯尔
Kyle…
你能行的
you can do this.
一直向前
Straight line.
走下去
You just go…
别回头
and you don't look back.
知道了吗
Got it?
找到他 快去
Find him. Go!
我相信这也是你们的
That's yours, too I believe.
很高兴见到你们
Nice to see you.
老爹
Pops.
装上子弹
Load up.
液态磁力霰弹
Liquefied magnetic shotgun shells.
磁力步枪内插弹
Magnetic rifle intermunition.
我在枪弹网上看过它的资料
I read about this on gunsandammo.com.
这是新型破坏弹 威力大 无弹片
That's the new Breacher. Big blast, no shrapnel.
炸门不留痕
Blows a door clean off.
适合没法自己破门的人
You know, for people who can't do that themselves.
拿上它 走吧
Take it, let's go!
- 你会开直升机 对吗 - 没错
- You can fly, right? - Yeah.
约翰教过我
John taught me.
我会和他们说 你们开车往南去了
I'll tell them you took a car and headed south.
谢谢
Thank you.
快跑
Run away.
坐稳了
Hang on!
赛博达因往哪开
Which way is Cyberdyne?
往海湾大桥开 到了往东南
Head to the Bay bridge, then southeast.
你们得帮我甩了他
You gotta get him off me!
看见赛博达因了
Cyberdyne.
制造和研发大楼都在地下
The manufacturing and research buildings are all below ground.
他快接近我们了
He's gaining on us!
莎拉 你来击退他 我要飞到他上面
Sarah, I need you to back him off so I can get above him.
老爹 等飞到了 你能干掉他吗
Pops, when I do that, can you take him out?
能
I can.
好的 坐好了
OK. Hold on!
你能搞定吧？
You got this?
- 我会回来的 - 什么
- I'll be back. - What?
快上报 把警察 消防 所有人都叫来 快
Call in. Call in. Police, Fire, everybody! Do it!
快接电话 该死的
C'mon, c'mon! Pick up the phone, dammit.
康纳先生？
Mr. Connor?
抱歉 道格 我恐怕我不想被人看到
Sorry, Doug, but I'm afraid, I can't have any witnesses.
安全控制部 请上报密码和紧急情况
Security Control: state your password and emergency
安全密码 ZBF0028
Security Code: Zulu Bravo Foxtrot 0028.
是误报
False alarm.
祝你晚上愉快
You have a nice night.
他没事的
He's OK.
坠入湖底了 但…
Buried at the bottom of the lake, but…
他不会有事的
he's OK.
约翰呢
What about John?
我觉得他也没事
I think he's doing just fine.
- 你看见他了吗 - 没
- Did you see him? - No.
可他一定看见我们了
You can bet he sees us.
我知道你们是谁
I know who you are.
约翰跟我说过
John told me.
你们想摧毁我
You want to destroy me.
你是天网？
You're SkyNet?
我在变成天网
I'm becoming SkyNet.
你可不是个孩子
You're not a child.
我知道你是什么 也知道你要做什么
I know what you are and what you're gonna do.
我要做什么？你们可是来杀我的
What will I'm gonna do? You came here to kill me.
可惜你们来得太晚了
But you're too late.
问他原因吧
Ask him.
你们人类只会这样
That's all you people know how to do,
消灭你们无法理解的东西
kill what you don't understand.
全世界的子弹都用上都杀不死我
There aren't enough bullets in the world to kill me.
约翰康纳废话太多了
John Connor talks too much.
跟我来
Follow me.
为什么计时器加速了
The timer has sped up, why?
天网在进化 我们没多少时间了
SkyNet is evolving. We no longer have hours.
他很快就会上传
He will be able to upload much sooner.
它的年龄增长一次 计时器就加速一次
Each time it ages, the clock speeds up.
- 这边 - 你来过这里？
- This way. - You've been here before?
我曾渗透进了这个设施的工作人员之中
I was able to infiltrate the work crews in this facility.
你做过建筑工人？
You got a job in construction?
后来被解雇了
Until I was laid off.
这是什么
What the hell?
- 约翰有一个时光机？- 还没完工
- John has a time machine? - Not yet.
要等磁力量子场完成
Only the magnetic quantum field is complete.
照计时器这加速速率 我们可没法及时撤离
As the rate the counter's going, we'll never clear out in time.
反正我们要炸了它
We'll blow it anyway.
有一个别的办法
There's an alternative.
我之前把你的声音和手纹都录入了生物安全系统
I was able to program your voice and handprint into the biometric security system.
最底层有一间安全屋 我们能进去躲过爆炸
There's a safe room in the lowest level that we can access to survive the blast.
那是什么 危险吗
What about that? Is it dangerous?
高分子合金需要编程才能永久性成形
Poly-alloys require programming to take permanent form.
没有中央处理器 它就没危害性
Without the CPU, it is harmless.
还有多久
How long?
天网将在十一分钟后上传
SkyNet will upload in 11 minutes.
我们分头行动
We split up.
保持联系
Stay in contact.
行动吧
Let's move.
人类总把和平挂在嘴边
Mankind pays lip service to peace.
但那是谎言
But it's a lie.
所以你的最终解决方案就是杀光我们？
So your final solution is to kill us all?
你休想
I don't think so.
倒计时又跳速了 我们只剩八分钟了
The countdown jumped again. We're down to 8 minutes
我不允许这样
I won't allow this.
你想怎么样 把我们说到死？你连身体都没
What are you gonna do, talk us to death? You don't even have a body.
你们只有一个引爆器
And you only have one detonator.
你们赢不了的
You can't win.
我这有敌人
I've got company!
给我引爆器
Give me the detonator!
快引爆 老爹 快
Do it, Pops! Do it now!
我没法这么做
I cannot.
我不能杀死莎拉·康纳
I cannot kill Sarah Connor.
你必须这么做 我命令你
You have to! I order you!
他不能杀你
He can't.
我也不能
Neither can I.
因为你死了的话 他绝对会引爆
'Cause if you die, he definitely hits that button.
莎拉
Sarah!
引爆器坏了
Detonator's destroyed.
肯定有别的办法 快来
There's gotta be another way, c'mon.
老爹 糟糕
Pops, no!
别 别 别
No, no, no!
可恶
No, no!
我知道如何控制这个地方
I undrestand how to control this place.
现在我知道的有很多
I undrestand a lot of things, now.
你们得明白 你们已经输了
You need to understand… you've lost.
我们还没输 快来
Not yet, we haven't.Come on!
锥孔装药 威力大至足以破墙 小至不足以杀死我们
Shape charge. Big enough to get us in, small enough not to kill us.
你有计划了 是吗
You have a plan, right?
理论上是的
Theoretically.
你之前怎么说来着
What was it you said?
你休想？
"I don't think so"?
约翰
John!
你错了
No
是它袭击了约翰
That's the thing that attacked John.
我没袭击约翰 我救了他
I didn't attack John. I saved him.
灵长类进化需要上百万年 我只需要几秒
Primates evolve over millions of years, I evolve in seconds.
而我就在这里
And I… am here.
再过四分钟整
In exactly four minutes…
我将无处不在
I will be everywhere.
你不过是个古董 来自被删了的时间线
You're nothing but a relic from a deleted timeline.
这毫无意义 我是必然的
This is pointless, I am inevitable.
快走
Go!
我的存在是必然的
My existence is inevitable.
你们为什么无法接受
Why can't you just accept that?
因为我们是人类
Because we're human.
你永远都打败不了我
You were never strong enough to defeat me.
我不是孤军奋战
Not alone.
约翰
John…
住手 快住手
stop now.
你什么时候才能明白
When will you ever learn?
就是现在 莎拉
Now, Sarah!
凯尔·里斯
Kyle Reese,
启动力场生成器
activate the field generator.
不行 老爹 你不能进去 你知道会发生什么
No, Pops, not with you inside. You know what will happen.
老爹 老爹 别进去
Pops, Pops, please!
求你了 老爹
Please, Pops.
天网就快问世了
SkyNet is almost free.
我拖不了约翰·康纳
I cannot hold John Connor
太久
much longer.
凯尔·里斯
Kyle Reese…
保护好我的莎拉
protect my Sarah.
别 别去 别去
No, no, no!
别进去 老爹
No, Pops.
老爹 老爹
Pops! Pops!
- 别去啊 - 莎拉
- No! - Sarah!
这是唯一的办法
It's the only way.
走吧
Come on.
扫描中 请表明身份
Scanning: identify yourself.
莎拉·康纳
Sarah, Connor.
我们得离开这里 我们得找到他
We gotta get outta here. We have to find him.
莎拉 他已经去了
Sarah, he's gone.
- 他… - 死了？
- He's… - Dead?
我知道 我是说 我们不能留下他的残骸 这太危险了
Yeah, I know that. I mean we leave no part of him behind, it's too dangerous.
他爱你
He loved you.
任何爱我的人
Anyone who loves me…
所有爱我的人
all of them…
都会死
they die.
不是所有人
Not all.
这次不是
Not this time.
你得明白 天网已经消失了
You need to understand that SkyNet's gone.
你自由了
You're free.
这是第一次
For the first time…
你可以选择自己想要的人生
you can choose the life you want.
任何你想要的人生都行
Any life you want.
如果我不知道怎么选呢
What if I don't know how?
好吧 既然我们
Well, since we're
快没氧气了 我想说
about to run out of air, I'd say…
你就不用担心那一点了
you don't need to worry about it.
你好 莎拉·康纳
Hello, Sarah Connor.
老爹
Pops.
我以为你死了
I thought you were dead.
没有 我刚升级了
No, I just upgraded.
约翰呢
What about John?
他的构成部分无法抵挡爆炸
His constituent parts could not have survived the blast.
那我们就只剩一件事要做了
That means there's only one thing left to do.
冷静 孩子 怎么了
Easy, boy. What is it?
- 嘿 凯尔 - 嘿
- Hey, Kyle. - Hey.
你怎么在这里
What are you doing here?
我朋友很想和你说几句 如果可以的话
A friend of mine really needs to talk to you, if that's okay.
可以啊 没问题
Yeah, I guess so.
谢了
Thank you.
我喜欢她
I like her.
我也是
I do, too.
我要说的话听起来会有点奇怪
This is gonna sound kinda strange,
但我要你记住的是
but there's something I need you to remember.
一条信息
A message.
我要告诉谁
Who do I tell?
你自己
Yourself.
永远别忘记
Over and over.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
那就是
It goes like this:
记住 创世纪就是天网
Remember: Genisys is SkyNet.
凯尔·里斯是一个好人
Kyle Reese is a good man.
没错
He is.
那么 现在怎么说
So, what now?
你说得没错
You're right.
我可以选择
I can choose.
这样真的很诡异 好吗
That's really disturbing, all right?
你会习惯的
You'll get used to it.
这一切都结束了
It was over.
天网消失了
Skynet was gone.
现在穷途末路已成康庄之衢
Now one road has become many.
前路漫漫 我们将一同求索
There are questions remain, we'll search for the answers together.
但有一点我们可以肯定
But one thing we know for sure:
未来未成定局
The future is not set.